Guide to the Challenge to Governance oral history project, 1969-1971.
Challenge to Governance oral history project
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Challenge to Governance oral history project, 1969-1971.
13-6-1285
Cornell University. Program in Oral History.
ca.100 tapes and Transcripts.
Tape recordings and Transcripts.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Over 100 interviews with students, faculty, staff, and administrators on subjects including the Vietnam War and the peace movement; the rights of women and minorities, especially blacks' rights and the militant takeover of Willard Straight; efforts to change the governing system at Cornell; and related issues. Most of the interviews have been transcribed.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Cornell University Libraries, represented by the Program in Oral History and the University Archives, collected primary source materials and conducted interviews concerning changes in the governance of the university due to campus activism during the late 1960s. The project was coordinated by University Archivist Herbert Finch and Cornell Program in Oral History Director Gould P. Colman. The goal of the oral history project was to bring within the project appropriate interviewers for members of the various interest groups at Cornell and subdivisions of those groups formed in the process of crisis. An effort was made to match potential respondents with compatible interviewers in order to respond quickly to a highly mobile population and rapidly changing events.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Over 100 interviews with students, faculty, staff, and administrators on subjects including the Vietnam War and the peace movement; the rights of women and minorities, especially blacks' rights and the militant takeover of Willard Straight; efforts to change the governing system at Cornell; and related issues. Most of the interviews have been transcribed.
Interviews (tapes and Transcripts) with John Marcham, Alice Cook, Sarah Elbert Diamant, Douglas Dowd, W. Robert Finegan, Paul Marantz, Sheila Tobias, William G. Tomlinson, Stephen Wallenstein, Mark Barlow, Max Black, Clinton Rossiter, Bruce Gelber, D. Peter Harvey, Eldon Kenworthy, William S. Myers, David Lyons, Franklin Moss, F. Dana Payne, Barbara Hirshfeld, Norman Penney, James W. Pewett, James L. Zwingle, Orval C French, Walter LaFeber, Santo J. Laquatra, Pearl E. Lucas, James H. Matlack, Steven Muller, Cushing Strout, Robin M. Williams, Jr., Peter Agree, Tom E. Davis, George H. Hildebrand, Margaret E. Keck, Hartwig E. Kisker, Albert S. Miles, Edwin B. Oyer, Joel H. Silbey, Walter J. Slatoff, John Lee Smith, Burton I. Weiss, Paul Olum, Jeffrey M. Blunt, Douglas N. Archibald, Susan Barcus Zebelman, Anthony Fels, Jane Friedman, Irving Gross, William D. Jones, Joseph H. Kelly, Thomas J. Leonard, Donald C. Mangold, Bryron G. McCalmon, Charles G. McCord, Mark F. Sharefkin, Arthur B. Spitzer, Thomas L. Tobin, Stuart M. Brown, Jr., Jack K. Kiely, Gerald W. Lattin, Charles C. Marshall, III, Matthew F. McHugh, Frank Rosenblatt, O. M. Ungers, Paul M. DuBois, George C. Hildebrand, Carl A. Anderson, Larry Cooper, Cleveland Donald, Jr., David L. Dupree, Myra E. Gordon, Houston Johnson, Jr., Eric R. Krystall, Peter J. Sharfman, William L. Stallworth, Herman Wilson, Rev. David W. Connor, Jean Failing, Elmer E. Meyer, Reeve Parker, Steven W. Telsey, Gary W. Bickel, Charisse Cannaday, Ruth W. Darling, Harry Edwards, Gloria I. Joseph. William J. Osby, George R. Pfann, Raymond G. Thorpe, John W. Wilkins, Michael J. Wright, Madeleine H. Zelin, R. D. Miller, Harold R. Capener, Joseph P. King, LeGrace G. Benson, and W. Keith Kennedy.
Tape recordings only of interviews with students Robert Brauner, "Concerned Faculty," Kristeena Dalby, Howard M. Feinstein, Sharon Goldberg, Julie Jordan, Robert Ordman, Psycho-History Students, and Sister Mary Thomas.
Interviewers include Jeffrey M. Blunt, Gould P. Colman, Sarah Elbert (Diamant), Howard M. Feinstein, William G. Tomlinson, Stephen Wallenstein, and Michael J. Wright.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Agree, Peter.; Anderson, Carl A.; Archibald, Douglas N.; Barlow, Mark, 1925-2012.; Benson, LeGrace G.; Benson, LeGrace G.; Bickel, Gary William.; Black, Max.; Blunt, Jeffrey.; Brauner, Robert; Brown, Stuart M., Jr.; Cannaday, Charisse.; Capener, Harold R. (Harold Rigby), 1919-; Colman, Gould P. (Gould Patchin), 1926-; Connor, David W.; Cook, Alice Hanson.; Cook, Alice Hanson.; Cooper, Larry.; Dalby, Kristeena.; Darling, Ruth W.; Davis, Thomas Edward.; Donald, Cleveland, Jr.; Dowd, Douglas Fitzgerald, 1919-; DuBois, Paul Martin, 1945-; Dupree, David L.; Edwards, Harry, 1942-; Elbert, Sarah.; Failing, Jean, 1913-; Feinstein, Howard M.; Fels, Anthony.; Finegan, W. Robert.; French, Orval C; Friedman, Jane.; Gelber, Bruce.; Goldberg, Sharon.; Gordon, Myra E.; Grossman, Irving.; Harvey, D. Peter.; Hildebrand, George C.; Hildebrand, George Herbert.; Hirshfeld, Barbara.; Johnson, Houston, Jr.; Jones, William D.; Jordan, Julie.; Joseph, Gloria I.; Keck, Margaret E.; Kelly, Joseph H.; Kennedy, Wilbert Keith, 1919-; Kenworthy, Eldon, 1935-; Kiely, Jack K.; King, Joseph P.; Kisker, Hartwig E.; Krystall, Eric R.; LaFeber, Walter.; Laquatra, Santo J.; Lattin, Gerald W.; Leonard, Thomas J.; Lucas, Pearl Elaine; Lyons, David, 1935-; Mangold, Donald Carl, 1945-; Marantz, Paul.; Marcham, John, 1927-; Marshall, Charles C. III.; Matlack, James Henerson.; McCalmon, Byron G.; McCord, Charles G.; McHugh, Matthew F. (Matthew Francis), 1938-; Meyer, Elmer Jr.; Miles, Albert S.; Miller, R. D. (Robert Demorest), 1919-2011.; Moss, Franklin.; Muller, Steven, 1927-2013.; Myers, William S.; Olum, Paul.; Ordman, Robert.; Osby, William J.; Oyer, Edwin B.; Parker, Reeve.; Payne, F. Dana.; Penney, Norman.; Pewett, James W.; Pfann, George R.; Rosenblatt, Frank.; Rossiter, Clinton.; Sharefkin, Mark F., 1917-1970.; Sharfman, Peter J.; Silbey, Joel H.; Slatoff, Walter J. (Walter Jacob), 1922-1991.; Smith, John Lee.; Spitzer, Arthur B.; Stallworth, William L.; Strout, Cushing.; Telsey, Steven W.; Thomas, Mary, Sister.; Thorpe, Raymond G.; Tobias, Sheila.; Tobin, Thomas L.; Tomlinson, William G.; Ungers, O. M. (Oswald Mathias); Wallenstein, Stephen.; Weiss, Burton I.; Wilkins, John W.; Williams, Robin M. Jr., 1914-2006.; Wilson, Herman.; Wright, Michael J.; Zebelman, Susan Barcus.; Zelin, Madeleine H.; Zwingle, J. L.; Cornell University -- History.; Cornell University -- Administration.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University. Constituent Assembly
Subjects:
Willard Straight Hall takeover, 1969.; African American student movements.; African Americans -- Education.; College students -- Political activity.; College students -- New York (State) -- Ithaca.; College student government.; Student movements.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Transcripts and tapes for Sarah Elbert (Diamant), Margaret E. Keck, Hartwig E. Kisker, Albert S. Miles, Joseph H. Kelly, Thomas J. Leonard, Charles C. Marshall, Larry Cooper, Myra E. Gordon, William L. Stallworth, Elmer E. Meyer Jr., Reeve Parker, Gary Bickel, Charisse Cannaday, Harry Edwards, Gloria I. Joseph, William J. Osby, John W. Wilkins, Madeleine H. Zelin, Harold R. Capener, and Joseph Kingrequire written permission to use.
Transcript and tape recording for Walter LaFeber is closed for all research until 5 years after the death of Professor LaFeber and his wife.
Transcript and tape recording for Franklin Mossmay not be used by law enforcement officials without written permission.
Tape recordings only for James W. Pewett, LeGrace Benson, Krysteena Dalby, Sharon Goldberg, and Robert Ordmanrequire written permission to use.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related collection:Challenge to Governance Project Records, #47-5-1309.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Alphabetical List of Participants
a. Last Names A-L\
b. Last Names M-Z
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Alphabetical List of Participants
  - Last Names A-L
    - Agree, Peter, 1969-05-14; TR-1543; Transcript-1543 (Box 18)
      Interviewed by: Diamant
      Role: Student
      Class Year: 1969
      School/Department: Industrial and Labor Relations
    - Anderson, Carl A., 1969-08-26; TR-1581; Transcript-1581 (Box 19)
      Interviewed by: Tomlinson
      Class Year: 1968
    - Archibald, Douglas N., 1969-07-11; TR-1558-1559; Transcript-1558-1559 (Box 18)
      Interviewed by: Wright
      Role: Professor, English
    - Barlow, Mark,1925-2012, 1969-07-14 - 1969-08-13; TR-1522-1524; Transcript-1522 (Box 17)
      Role: VP Student Affairs
    - Benson, LeGrace G.,1930-, 1970-12-04; TR-1624 R; Transcript-1624 (Box 21)
      Interviewed by: Colman
      Role: Asst Professor, Hist of Art
      Class Year: Ph.D. 1974
      School/Department: College of Agriculture and Life Sciences
    - Bickel, Gary William,1932-, 1970-02-19; TR-1597-1598; Transcript-1597 (Box 20)
      Interviewed by: Blunt
      Role: Professor, Economics
      Access Restrictions
    - Black, Max,1909-1988, 1969-08-01; TR-1525; Transcript-1525 (Box 17)
      Interviewed by: Wallenstein
      Role: Professor, Philosophy
    - Blunt, Jeffrey M., 1969-06-02; TR-1557; Transcript-1557 (Box 18)
      Interviewed by: Self
      Class Year: 1972
    - Brauner, Robert, 1969-07-01; TR-1613
      Class Year: 1971
      School/Department: English
    - Brown, Stuart M., Jr.,1916-1996, 1969-10-14; TR-1572; Transcript-1572 (Box 19)
      Role: VP Academic Affairs
    - Cannaday, Charisse, 1969-06-23; TR-1599; Transcript-1599 (Box 20)
      Role: COSEP
    - Capener, Harold R. (Harold Rigby),1919-, 1969-07-31; TR-1622; Transcript-1622 (Box 21)
      Role: Professor, Rural Soc.
    - Concerned Faculty, 1969-06-16; TR-1611
      Interviewed by: Feinstein
    - Connor, Rev. David W., 1969-06-26; TR-1591; Transcript-1591 (Box 20)
      Role: CURW
      Class Year: 1959
      Transcript digitized
    - Cook, Alice Hanson,1903-1998, 1971-06-16 - 1971-09-29; TR-1514; Transcript-1514 (Box 17)
      Role: Professor, ILR
    - Cooper, Larry, 1969-08-20; TR-1582; Transcript-1582 (Box 20)
      School/Department: College of Arts and Sciences
    - Dalby, Kristeena, 1969-07-09; TR-1596
      R
    - Darling, Ruth W.,1912-1998, 1969-07-26 - 1969-08-29; TR-1600-1601; Transcript-1600 (Box 20)
      Role: Assoc. Dean of Students
    - Davis, Tom Edward, 1929-, 1969-08-18; TR-1544; Transcript-1544 (Box 18)
    - Diamant, Sarah Elbert, 1937-, 1969-06-09; TR-1515; Transcript-1515 (Box 17)
      Role: Graduate Student
      Class Year: 1964, Ph.D. 1974
    - Donald, Cleveland, Jr.,1946-2012, 1969-07-14; TR-1583; Transcript-1583 (Box 20)
      Class Year: Ph.D. 1973
      Digitized
    - Dowd, Douglas Fitzgerald, 1919-, 1969-06-13; TR-1516; Transcript-1516 (Box 17)
    - DuBois, Paul Martin,1945-, 1969-07-30; TR-1579; Transcript-1579 (Box 19)
      Class Year: Ph.D. 1977
    - Dupree, David L., 1969-08-14; TR-1584; Transcript-1584 (Box 20)
      Class Year: 1970
    - Edwards, Harry ,1942-, 1969-12-01; TR-1602; Transcript-1602 (Box 20)
      Class Year: 1966/MA1973
    - Failing, Jean, 1913-,1913-2008, 1969-08-11; TR-1592; Transcript-1592 (Box 20)
      Role: Assoc. Dean Undergrad Ed
    - Fels, Anthony, 1969-06-06; TR-1561; Transcript-1561 (Box 19)
    - Finegan, W. Robert, 1969-06-19; TR-1517; Transcript-1517 (Box 17)
      Role: Dir. Development Communications
    - French, Orval C,1908-1999, 1969-07-25; TR-1535; Transcript-1535 (Box 17)
      Role: Professor, Ag. Engineering
    - Friedman, Jane, 1969-05-23; TR-1562R; Transcript-1562 (Box 19)
      Role: Student, U Penn
    - Gelber, Bruce, 1969-05-31; TR-1526; Transcript-1526 (Box 17)
    - Goldberg, Sharon, 1969-07-02; TR-1613
      Interviewed by:
      Restricted
    - Gordon, Myra E., 1969-07-20; TR-1585; Transcript-1585 (Box 20)
      Class Year: 1972 (74)
    - Grossman, Irving, 1969-08-22; TR-1563; Transcript-1563 (Box 19)
      Role: Ithaca resident
    - Harvey, D. Peter, 1969-06-06; TR-1527R; Transcript-1527 (Box 17)
      Interviewed by: Marantz
    - Hildebrand, George C., 1969-08-19; TR-1580; Transcript-1580 (Box 19)
      Class Year: MA 1971
    - Hildebrand, George Herbert,1913-2007, 1969-09-13; TR-1545; Transcript-1545 (Box 18)
    - Hirshfeld, Barbara (Babcock),1918-2008, 1969-07-18; TR-1531; Transcript-1531 I (Box 17)
      Role: Assistant Dean, A&S
      Class Year: 1939
    - History Grad Students, 1969-05; TR-1614
    - Johnson, Houston, Jr., 1969-07-07; TR-1586; Transcript-1586 (Box 20)
    - Jones, William D.,1928-2008, 1969-07-17; TR-1564; Transcript-1564 (Box 19)
      Role: Asst to Provost, COSEP
      Class Year: MPA 1979
      School/Department: Johnson Graduate School of Management
    - Jordan, Julie, 1969-08-08; TR-1612
    - Joseph, Gloria I., 1969-07-01 - 1969-10-31; TR-1603; Transcript-1603 (Box 20)
      Role: COSEP Director
      Class Year: Ph.D. 1967
    - Keck, Margaret E., 1969-06-20; TR-1546; Transcript-1546 (Box 18)
    - Kelly, Joseph H., 1969-08-10; TR-1565; Transcript-1565 (Box 19)
      Class Year: 1967
    - Kennedy, Wilbert Keith ,1919-2011, 1971-09-15; Transcript-5346-5347
    - Kennedy, Wilbert Keith ,1919-2011, 1970-03-18; TR-1628-1629; Transcript-1628-1629 (Box 21)
      Role: Vice Provost
    - Kenworthy, Eldon ,1935-1998, 1969-08-01; TR-1528; Transcript- 1528 I (Box 17)
      Role: Professor, Government
    - Kiely, Jack K.,1928-1987, 1969-06-27; TR-1573; Transcript-1573 (Box 19)
      Role: Mayor of Ithaca
    - King, Joseph P.,1910-1990, 1969-10-28; TR-1623; Transcript-1623 (Box 21)
      Role: Alumnus
      Class Year: 1936
    - Kisker, Hartwig E., 1969-06-17 - 1969-07-03; TR-1547-1548; Transcript-1547 (Box 18)
      Role: Judicial administrator
    - Kisker, Hartwig E., 1971-10-21; TR-1621 R; Transcript-1621 (Box 21)
    - Krystall, Eric R.,1928-, 1969-06-04; Transcript-1587 (Box 20)
      Role: Visiting Prof (South Africa)
    - LaFeber, Walter, 1969-07-25; TR-1536; Transcript-1536 (Box 18)
      Interviewed by: Marantz +
      Role: Professor, History
    - LaFeber, Walter, 1970-02-06; Transcript-1536 II (Box 18)
    - Laquatra, Santo J., 1969-07-09; TR-1537; Transcript-1537 (Box 18)
      School/Department: Hotel
    - Lattin, Gerald W.,1921-2013, 1969-07-23; TR-1574; Transcript-1574 (Box 19)
      Role: Asst Dean, Hotel
      Class Year: Ph.D. 1949
    - Leonard, Thomas J., 1969-07-09; TR-1566; Transcript-1566 (Box 19)
    - Lucas, Pearl Elaine, 1969-07-03; TR-1538; Transcript-1538 (Box 18)
      Role: Asst Dean, A&S
      Class Year: M.A. 1974
    - Lyons, David,1935-, 1969-07-31; TR-1529; Transcript-1529 (Box 17)
      Role: Professor, Law
  - Last Names M-Z
    - Mangold, Donald Carl,1945-, 1969-08-26; TR-1567; Transcript-1567 (Box 19)
    - Marantz, Paul, 1969-05-25; TR-1518; Transcript-1518 (Box 17)
      Role: Visiting Prof, Government
    - Marcham, John,1927-2014, 1969-07-08; TR-1513; Transcript-1513 (Box 17)
      Role: Editor, Alumni News
      Class Year: 1950
    - Marshall, Charles C. III, 1969-06-26; TR-1575; Transcript-1575 (Box 19)
      Class Year: 1967 (68)
    - Matlack, James Hendrickson, 1969-07-02; TR-1539; Transcript-1539 (Box 18)
    - McCalmon, Byron G., 1969-07-29; TR-1568; Transcript-1568 I (Box 19)
      Role: Asst Dir. Financial Aid
    - McCord, Charles G.,1934-2013, 1969-07-29; TR-1568; Transcript-1568 II (Box 19)
      Role: Placement Director
    - McHugh, Matthew F. (Matthew Francis),1938-, 1969-06-30; TR-1576; Transcript-1576 (Box 19)
      Role: Tompkins County DA
    - Meyer Jr., Elmer E.,1928-2012, 1969-06-12 - 1969-07-29; TR-1593-1594; Transcript-1593-1594 (Box 20)
      Interviewed by: Feinstein & Wright
      Role: Asst. VP for Student Affairs
    - Miles, Albert S., 1969-06-26; TR-1549; Transcript-1549 (Box 18)
      Role: Asst Dean of Students
      Class Year: Ph.D.1969
    - Miller, R. D. (Robert Demorest),1919-2011, 1969-07-30 - 1970-01-16; TR-1617-1620; Transcript-1617-1620 (Box 21)
      Role: Dean of the Faculty
      Class Year: Ph.D. 1948
    - Moss, Franklin, 1969-07-06; TR-1530; Transcript-1530 (Box 17)
    - Muller, Steven,1927-2013, 1969-07-30; TR-1540; Transcript-1540 (Box 18)
      Role: Vice President Public Affairs
    - Myers, William S., 1969-07-31; TR-1528; Transcript-1528 II (Box 17)
      School/Department: Law
    - Olum, Paul,1918-2001, 1969-07-25 - 1970-02-19; TR-1555-1556; Transcript-1555-1556 (Box 18)
      Interviewed by: Wallenstein & Colman
      Role: Professor, Math
    - Ordman, Robert, 1969-08-10; TR-1560
    - Osby, William J., 1970-02-05 - 1970-05-05; TR-1604-1605; Transcript-1604 (Box 21)
      Role: Graduate Student, CRP
      Class Year: Ph.D 1977
      School/Department: Art, Architecture, and Planning
    - Oyer, Edwin B., 1969-07-14; TR-1550; Transcript-1550 (Box 18)
      Role: Professor, Vegetable Crops
    - Parker, Reeve, 1969-07-15; TR-1595; Transcript-1595 (Box 20)
    - Payne, F. Dana,1923-1988, 1969-07-18; TR-1531; Transcript-1531 I (Box 17)
      Role: Assoc. Dean A&S
    - Penney, Norman, 1926-,1926-1981, 1969-07-18; TR-1531; Transcript-1531 II (Box 17)
      Role: Acting Dean, Law
      Class Year: 1953 JD
    - Pewett, James W., 1969-06-21; TR-1532 R; Transcript-1532 (Box 17)
      Interviewed by: Breydrick
      Role: Student, Govt.
    - Pfann, George R.,1902-1996, 1969-07-11; TR-1606; Transcript-1606 (Box 21)
      Role: Trustee (Alumni)
      Class Year: 1924
    - Psycho-History Students, TR-1615
    - Rosenblatt, Frank,1928-1971, 1969-07-14; TR-1577; Transcript-1577 (Box 19)
      Role: Professor, Neurobiology
    - Rossiter, Clinton,1917-1970, 1969-08-01; TR-1525; Transcript-1525 I (Box 17)
    - Sharefkin, Mark F., 1969-07-02; TR-1569; Transcript-1569 (Box 19)
      Class Year: M.A. 1972
    - Sharfman, Peter J., 1969-07-28; TR-1588; Transcript-1588 (Box 20)
    - Silbey, Joel H., 1969-09-05; TR-1551; Transcript-1551 (Box 18)
    - Slatoff, Walter J. (Walter Jacob),1922-1991, 1969-06-27; TR-1552; Transcript-1552 (Box 18)
    - Smith, John Lee,1928-2010, 1969-08-26; TR-1553; Transcript-1553 (Box 18)
      Role: CURW Assoc. Dir.
    - Spitzer, Arthur B., 1969-06-27; TR-1570; Transcript-1570 (Box 19)
    - Stallworth, William L, 1969-07-28; TR-1589; Transcript-1589 (Box 20)
    - Strout, Cushing,1923-2013, 1969-07-04; TR-1541; Transcript-1541 (Box 18)
    - Telsey, Steven W., 1969-07-10; TR-1596; Transcript-1596 (Box 20)
      Role: Ombudsman (Asst for Info)
    - Thomas, Sister Mary, 1969-05-23; TR-1616
    - Thorpe, Raymond G.,1921-2005, 1969-08-25; TR-1607; Transcript-1607 (Box 21)
      Role: Professor, Chem. Engineering
    - Tobias, Sheila, 1969-07-15; TR-1519; Transcript-1519 (Box 17)
      Role: Asst to VP Academic Affairs
    - Tobin, Thomas L., 1969-07-07 - 1969-07-29; TR-1571; Transcript-1571 (Box 19)
      Role: Dir. Public Information
    - Tomlinson, William G.,1943-2012, 1969-07-08; TR-1520; Transcript-1520 (Box 17)
      Class Year: 1968 MS 1971
      School/Department: College of Arts and Sciences/College of Agriculture and Life Sciences
    - Ungers, O. M. (Oswald Mathias),1926-2007, 1969-07-22; TR-1578; Transcript-1578 (Box 19)
      Role: Professor, Architecture
    - Wallenstein, Stephen, 1969-06-28; TR-1521; Transcript-1521 (Box 17)
    - Weiss, Burton I.,1945-2011, 1969-06-26; TR-1554; Transcript-1554 (Box 18)
    - Wilkins, John W., 1969-06-20; TR-1608; Transcript-1608 (Box 21)
      Role: Professor, Physics
    - Williams, Robin M., Jr.,1914-2006, 1969-08-11; TR-1542; Transcript-1542 (Box 18)
      Role: Professor, Sociology
    - Wilson, Herman, 1969-07-13; TR-1590; Transcript-1590 (Box 20)
    - Wright, Michael J., 1969-08-21; TR-1609; Transcript-1609 (Box 21)
      Role: Staff, Sociology
      Class Year: 1968 (69)
    - Zebelman, Susan Barcus, 1970-07-28; TR-1560; Transcript-1560 (Box 19)
    - Zelin, Madeleine H., 1970-01-28; TR-1610; Transcript-1610 (Box 21)
    - Zwingle, James L'Woods ,1906-1990, 1969-02-17 - 1969-06-16; TR-1533-1534; Transcript-1533 (Box 17)
      Role: Vice President